Curriculum Vitae

ARVIND NAUTIYAL

House No.93, Suneel,

PO-Joshimath, District-Chamoli, (U.K) 246443

Phone No.: +91 7240878740 Email: - notyarvind99@gmail.com

OBJECTIVE:-

To undertake challenges, expand experience and seek opportunities to develop a career in Human Recourse development and personal management, Apply diverse experience and knowledge to make a significant positive contribution towards the company continue personal development to enhance career advancement potential.

EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATION:-

- Senior Secondary education from U.K board in 2007.
- Higher secondary education from U.K board in 2005.
- Graduation from H.N.B.G.U in 2009.

PROFESSIONAL KNOWLEDGE AND SKILL:-

- Good knowledge of computer, MS office, MSexcel, internet and Hindi typing.
- Self-motivated with positive and practical approach.
- Like to accept new challenges.
- Confidence, creativity and interpersonal skills.
- Ability to lead as well as work with people as a team..

LANGUAGES KNOWN:-

• Hindi, Garhwali, English.

HOBBIES:-

- Cricket & Singing Song.
- Walking in the hills Area.

WORK EXPERIENCE:-

GCC Pvt Ltd Sriganganagar (RJ)

"Construction of 6-lane access controlled Greenfield Highway from Km 53+000 to Km 88+000 of Sangariya (Near Chautala)- Rasisar (near Bikaner) Section of NH-754K as a part of Amritsar- Jamnagar Economic Corridor in the State of Rajasthan on EPC mode under Bharatmala Pariyojna (Phase-1) (AJ/SR-Package -3)".

06 Jul 2020 To Till Date

Project - 06 Lane Bharatmala Road Project Pkg-03 NH-754

Organization - GCC Pvt. Ltd.

Department - HR

Designation - Executive (HR)

Dilip Buildcon Ltd Bhopal (MP)

India's well-known Corporate Services Company & a service industry based in India and provides facility management services and manpower services to large corporate in India.

04 Jan 2020 To 05 Jul 2020

Project - Bundelkhand Expressway Six Laning to Km 45.000 of UPEIDA in the

State of Uttar Pradesh under NHAI.

Organization - Dilip Buildcon Limited.

Department - HR

Designation - Executive

08 Nov 2017 To 02 Jan 2020

Project - Four Laning of Kathghora-Shivnagar Section of NH-111 from Km

82.000 to Km 162.000 of NH-111 in the state of Chhattisgarh under NHAI (National Highways Authority of India) Phase IV on BOT(Toll)on DBFOT (Design-Build-Finance-Operate-Transfer) Pattern.

Organization - Dilip Buildcon Limited.

Department - HR

Designation - Executive.

24 Aug 2016 To 06 Nov 2017

Project - Four Laningof Shivpuri to Guna Section of NH-3 from Km 0.000 to Km

30.000 of NH-3 in the state of Madhya Pradesh under NHDP (National Highways Development Project) Phase IV on BOT (Toll) on DBFOT

(Design-Build-Finance-Operate-Transfer) Pattern.

Organization - Dilip Buildcon Limited.

Client - Ircon International Ltd Shivpuri-Guna Toll Road Pvt. Ltd

Department - HR

Designation - Executive (AMS)

08 Nov 2014 To 23 Aug 2016

Project - Four Laning of Gwalior to ShivpuriSection of NH-3 from Km 0.000

to Km 125.000 of NH-3 in the state of Madhya Pradesh under NHDP (National Highways Development Project) Phase IV on BOT (Toll) on DBFOT (Design-Build-Finance-Operate-Transfer) Pattern.

Organization - Dilip Buildcon Limited

Client - Essel Gwalior-Shivpuri Toll Road Pvt. Ltd.

Department - HR

Designation - Executive (AMS)

Windlass Steel Crafts Dehradun (UK)

07 Jun 2012 To 12 Sep 2014

Experience of Maintain Labor Attendance Sheet and Payment Sheet.

Department - ATTENDANCE

Designation - Supervisor

ACHIEVEMENT:-

- Arranging Security Guards, Drivers, Operators, Mechanic, Helper for Company Requirements.
- Maintaining Employee **Attendance**, **Leave Record**, **Preparing Salary Sheet**, **No Dues (Exit)** Processing in **SAP** (Systems, Applications & Products in Data Processing).
- Generate New Join Employees ESIC & EPF (UAN).
- Daily attendance tracking thru **Bio metric machine**.
- Employee New joining database details send on day to day base to corporate office.
- Attrition analysis, Retention plan for attrition control.
- EPF withdrawals of left Employees and PF Nomination
- Distribute Declaration Form, FORM -16, Salary Cheque, HRA Cheque.
- Co-ordinate and ensure attendance for all **Daily Wages Labour & Sub-contractors Labour.**
- Day to Day Updated Daily Wages Labour & Sub-contractors Labour Attendance In SAP.
- Maintain Daily Wages Labour Payment Sheet.
- Checking Daily Wages Labour & Sub-contractors Labours, Adhar Card, Age Certificate & Bank Details.
- Insist to Employees for open Salary Account & Co-ordinate with Bank Executives.
- Maintain Mess Diet Sheet & Mess Management Facilities Checking.
- Supervision of Site Workers Supervisor Engineers & Labours Work.
- Manage Location Wise Security Guards Duty & Inspection of Guard Duty.

PERSONAL DETAIL:-

Father's Name : Shri Trilok Chandra Nautiyal

Birth Date : 5th July, 1988

Gender : Male

Marital Status : Unmarried

Religion : Hindu

Mother Tongue : Hindi

Nationality : Indian

Net Payment : 26000/-

DECLARATION:-

I hereby declare that the above given information is true and best of my knowledge.

.

DATE-31.08.2021 PALACE – JOSHIMATH (U.K)

Arvind Nautiyal